promotionalcodes.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - PromotionalCodes.com

3/14/2015 5:00:58 PM

### Your privacy is important to us.

PromotionalCodes.com has created this statement to illustrate our dedication to your privacy. We want you to be informed of the steps we take to protect your personal information. This privacy policy will thus explain how promotionalCodes.com uses and protects any personal information you choose to share with us by entering our website.PromotionalCodes.com understands the importance of privacy. We assure you that should we ask you to provide us with any personal or identifying information, such information will only be used in a manner specified in this privacy statement.

### Data Collection

#### Coupon Comments

You are by no means obligated to share any personal information on this website. However, there is one area where, if you like, you may comment on a coupon offer. In order to make your comment seem more personal and easier to reply to you are asked to enter a user name and a state of residence to go along with your comment. You are not required to enter a name or place and if you choose to leave these fields blank your comment will still be posted anonymously. However, should you choose to enter this information PromotionalCodes.com assures you that neither your name nor location will be shared with any other parties.

#### Cookies

Our site's visitors should know that PromotionalCodes.com uses cookies to recognize the computers used to gain access to our site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored via a user's web browser. We use cookies in an effort to simplify our internet transactions and make your experience with our site more personalized. In some cases, the user must click on the “Get Coupon” button to view the coupon ode or activate the discount; this is when the cookie drop occurs.

#### Email Newsletter

No personal information of any kind is required to use the Site. However, if you wish to receive the PromotionalCodes.com newsletter, a name, ZIP code, and email address are required. Your personal information including name, email address and ZIP code will never be shared with any other brands, including third parties, affiliates, partners, parent companies or subsidiaries for marketing purposes. All personal information collected by the user will never be transferred to third party companies. You can opt out of the email newsletter program at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" button located at the bottom of the email newsletter. PromotionalCodes.com abides by the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.

#### Website Redirects

It is also important for users to note that PromotionalCodes.com features links to various other retailer websites. We do this in order to make your online shopping experience faster and easier. After clicking on the featured retailer link you will be directed to the website of that retailer. Be aware that once on the linked website you are subject to the privacy policy of that retailer, not that of PromotionalCodes.com. PromotionalCodes.com has no control over those retailers' privacy policies. We thus encourage you to read their privacy policy statements upon entering their websites to make sure that you are comfortable with their policies. Since PromotionalCodes.com has no control over other merchant websites' policies we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you choose to disclose while visiting such sites and other sites not included in this privacy statement.

### Disclaimer

Please note that, in some cases, an item was supplied by the manufacturer and / or a fee was paid for the review or content within the associated blogs. PromotionalCodes.com reserves the right to alter or remove this privacy policy at our discretion. To remain informed of any updates to this statement we recommend that you visit our privacy policy page from time to time.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this statement… reach out to us at [contact@surfmyads.com](mailto:contact@surfmyads.com)
